<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>solochrome</title>
    <description>a sex and discovery blog
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 20:25:35 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 20:25:35 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>njoy Pure Wand Review</title>
        <description>&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;I’d placed the box in my nightstand before I’d even used it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It came in a day, with free shipping from Peepshow Toys, via an awesome deal ($79 for the Pure Wand and a 2 oz container of The Butters Lube).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few weeks later I’d considered my preemptive nightstand placement a bit of a mistake. I’d made an assumption that I’d love the Wand so much it’d end up there shortly anyway, so let’s just skip the formalities, huh? Thing is, I didn’t quite like this legend of a toy much until somewhat recently&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. I feel like I finally “got” it, and now having that black box in my nightstand feels right. Despite my rocky introduction to the toy, I had decided to keep it there and to try to learn how to use it better. See, I’d read tons of reviews on the Pure Wand, and a few mentioned that there’s a “learning curve”&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; to getting the most out of it. I had to give it the old college try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The thing is, the Pure Wand has such lofty status in the sex blogging world that I immediately thought that I should keep trying instead of putting it to the side as “not for me.” It couldn’t be, &lt;em&gt;it’s the njoy Pure Wand.&lt;/em&gt; I just want to put it out there–some people really might not like this toy and won’t ever ‘learn’ to. This is fine. So although I’ve come to like my Pure Wand a lot more, I think it’s expensive enough that if you don’t feel confident in taking the $80-$120 plunge … don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least not yet. Try a curved-n-bulbed glass toy, tons of which can be had at almost any price point&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:3&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. This is what I did, with the Gläs Double-Headed dildo. My enjoyment of that dildo also had me holding out hope that the Pure Wand could feel really good for me. Happily, it does now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/njoy_h.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I’ve heated the Pure Wand and have it slicked with lube that melts on contact, and finally press it inside me, the weight behind that first dip is wonderful. It’s a unique sensation that accompanies penetration when compared to other toys that I have to push or maneuver myself onto (the shape of each toy is obviously a factor here too).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Pure Wand settles inside me along its curve, which allows for intense-feeling sensation without a lot of work. I find myself moving my hand less than an inch or so when I find a spot I like. Whichever end acts as the handle, I can use to move the bulb inside me around (literally, like in ellipses or circles), or from side to side. And, of course, there’s good-ol’ thrusting. Depending on the angle I hold the Wand at, thrusting is more or less ‘disruptive’ internally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And what the fuck does that mean? Imagine two different angles for thrusting. You can sort of navigate your internal curves and by-ways with the head of the curve of the Pure Wand itself … or you can keep the Wand’s curve stationary while you move the toy in and out. The second one ends up hooking or digging into your walls a lot more heavily. One advantage that the gentler curve of a dildo shaped like my Gläs is that fast, smooth thrusting is more of a practical possibility with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find the Pure Wand a good deal more enjoyable if I heat it up before use. Even better is using the small end(or another dildo) to warm up, then using the big end. Some people use a vibrator with theirs, but I find that distracting in a way. It helps to actually get a little aroused before playing in earnest … something I ignored/forgot to do. To enjoy my Pure Wand, I have to be patient and use small movements; my first few forays into njoy-land, I was definitely riding on my expectations and habit (manic thrusting I employ[ed] with some of my other toys).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can buy the Pure Wand at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.peepshowtoys.com#oid=91554_4244&quot;&gt;Peepshow Toys&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bevibrant.com/products/njoy-pure-wand-dildo?rfsn=1509055.df2dc&amp;amp;utm_source=refersion&amp;amp;utm_medium=affiliate&amp;amp;utm_campaign=1509055.df2dc&quot;&gt;Vibrant&lt;/a&gt;, or practically anywhere else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;My first attempt at reviewing the Pure Wand contained sentences like: “As surprising as it may be, at this point in time, I can definitely say I’ve had a better time with my Gläs toy than with my Pure Wand.” &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Most notably &lt;a href=&quot;https://heyepiphora.com/2010/07/my-love-the-pure-wand-plus-a-few-tips&quot;&gt;Hey Epiphora&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:3&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Gläs makes cheap toys in a few good shapes, and on Etsy there are decently-priced options as well. Plus, you can even get something custom. Otherwise, there are usually curved glass toys available wherever you buy toys. And of course, there’s Icicles by Pipedream, but Pipedream sucks. It’s your decision though. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:3&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/njoy-pure-wand-review</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/njoy-pure-wand-review</guid>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fun Factory Tiger Review</title>
        <description>&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;The Tiger had intrigued me for months before I finally bought it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As my first and only Fun Factory toy so far, I didn’t know what to expect w/r/t the feel or texture of the silicone, or the rigidity of the toy. I have to say, the Tiger’s silicone is perfectly formulated as a counterbalance to its texture. &lt;!--break--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The shaft is flexible, yet doesn’t yield much to pressure. The Tiger isn’t a small toy, either, so the flexibility helps without taking away from one’s experience of Tiger’s 1.75” ø[^1](Diameter.). On the other hand, this isn’t the toy for pressuring whatever internal spot makes your jaw drop. You can stroke the fuck out of it with that crowning ridge, though! The silicone is slick, not matte or grainy, which lets the real texture of the Tiger come through without irritation. It doesn’t ‘eat’ lube like I’ve read that some of FF’s matte silicone can do.
But does the texture feel good?
I can tell you I love that top ridge that juts out from the ‘head’ of the Tiger, but the rest of the bumps don’t do much for me. They’re not enough to irritate my vaginal opening, but they don’t really add to the pleasure of using the Tiger. When I fuck myself with the Tiger, I feel the ridge, the length/girth, and the somewhat contradictory way that it fits inside me comfortably while feeling substantial.
At $50-60, I think the Tiger is worth it if you know you like texture but want something that you can use without being bowled over by irritating details or waves/bumps so large you can’t comfortably thrust.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/fun-factory-tiger</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/fun-factory-tiger</guid>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tantus Ripple Review</title>
        <description>&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;I like the Ripple; the small size means it’s perfect for ‘cold’ use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When using it for the first time, I discovered how much I like the undulating shape of the toy, despite the small size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;!–-break-–&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Surprisingly(to me, anyway), I really enjoy even going from bead #1 to #2. 2 to 3 is even better. Because the base is round and, I think because of the size of my ass lol, is practically impossible to get flush with my anus, I think of the Ripple as more of a small anal dildo. I imagine this would be even more true of the larger incarnation of the Ripple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tantus isn’t the only manufacturer of this type of anal toy: like their Silk series, there are several companies that make comparable options. Thing is, Tantus silicone and ethical standing is top-notch, where some of the other bead-dildo types of toys don’t come from companies that exclusively produce body-safe toys by hand, in the USA. Tantus is also widely available and the chances of getting a Ripple at a good price is pretty high. BS Atelier, another excellent company, makes a slightly thicker toy with a similar profile, the Bobó. It’s pretty, but it’s a bit more expensive than the Ripple large on Shevibe. It’s justifiable, though: one big leg-up the Bobó does have over both Ripples is the bar-type base, allowing for comfortable wear between the cheeks. Additionally, it comes in rainbow(!) and doesn’t have the length of the Ripple (l) while approaching its maximum width (1.25” vs 1.5”). More length can be uncomfortable or undesireable in anal toys, so I see this as a plus. I definitely can’t, and wouldn’t like to, take over 6” of the Ripple large to get the benefit of that last 1.5”-thick bead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I definitely bought the Ripple with ‘sizing up’ in mind; I’d never played with appropriately-sized anal toys before, and thought the graduated-bead approach would be manageable in ways that a tapered dildo/plug would not be. This is true, I think, but the Ripple does end up delivering a pleasure all its own that makes it a worthwhile buy. It’s a perfect gentle warm up, it feels good, it’s fun and interesting to play with the bloops, and it comes with all the inherent benefits of Tantus toys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Definitely recommend as a starter anal toy–you can get a little more fun out of this if you’re not specifically looking for a plug to wear. Thrusting it feels great and there’s the Ripple large to graduate to if you like the idea of using it to learn to take even larger toys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pick up the Ripple Small at Tantus for some Grab Bag excitement!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/tantus-ripple</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/tantus-ripple</guid>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tantus Echo &amp; Echo Super Soft Reviews</title>
        <description>&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;The Tantus Echo and Echo Super Soft are surprisingly different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My latest purchase from Tantus was a Grab Bag Echo–I ended up receiving an Echo Super Soft in what looks like Midnight Purple instead of the normal firmness. Tantus sent me a normal Echo in Purple Haze after that, so I get to review both here!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;!–-break-–&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Incidentally, the Echo Super Soft(SS) normally comes in Purple Haze or Wine, while the Echo is available in Midnight Purple or Pearly White. So the textures of my two Echoes are switched. Neat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Echo is very firm, as is typical for Tantus toys. It’s just a step or two away from completely rigid, and stands up on its own with no problem. The SS, on the other hand, can flop all over the place, and feels a lot less stable if you try to get it to stand on its own. It can, it’s just that the difference is palpable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When using my Tantus dildos, all of which have space for a vibrator, I usually put a finger in there while holding the base of the dildo as I thrust. The Echo is like my Tsunami: I can press as much as I like from the inside of the dildo–the walls won’t give. With the SS, I can actually feel(with my vagina/etc) my fingers’ movement and positioning against the walls of the toy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The matte finish of the SS can make it difficult to tell the difference in the depth of the toy’s texture, compared with the original Echo. Between the super-softness and the mellowed-out waves on the Echo Super Soft, I can’t feel the texture in use. The best thing about this dildo for me is the solid, yet soft head; I’ve found it feels great anally. In fact, I’ve been on something of a side-quest since I found out how much my ass likes soft silicone–all thanks to my accidental Echo SS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been a little let down by the original Echo as well. What I’ve learned about myself and my vagina is that I need a curve, not texture. The Echo looked like it would be my new obsession, but it doesn’t work as well for me as I’d thought. Apparently, I need my dildos to have a curve, and texture can just be a bonus on top of that, like with the Tantus Tsunami or the Fun Factory Tiger. So with the Echo SS, I honestly feel almost nothing when I use it vaginally–especially if my fingers aren’t in the vibrator-cavity, because then the weaker walls of the bottom part of the dildo seem to give in to my vaginal walls, instead of the other way around. At least with the original Echo I can get some sensation out of it. (I find it works best for me in certain positions and with quick, short thrusts.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Echo: hardly needs to be mentioned with Tantus, but the silicone is quality and, in the case of Purple Haze, gorgeous. It’s firm and the texture is noticable without being irritating, because it’s so exaggerated. This really depends on what you like–but personally, lighter texturing like on realistic dildos doesn’t feel good, just annoying. The texture on the Tiger, for me, is just enough to not be irritating in that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;notice&quot;&gt;Most importantly, though: if you want the Echo for g-spot stimulation, you might want to make sure that you can get the stimulation you’re after with a straight toy. If you’re looking for a killer g-spot toy, I think the Tsunami hits it much more intensely and reliably.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for texture, the Echo SS is disappointing. However, it is definitely a more gentle experience when thrusting, and if that works for you–the Echo SS probably will too. The softness is nice for anal as well, but the vibrator-cavity poses a real problem for me. It makes it harder to thrust and control the dildo, so if you want the softness with a more sturdy foundation to work with, you probably want to take a look at Tantus’ O2 and non-vibrator Super Soft toys. What I know about the Super Soft texture now has me lusting after a Severin Super Soft. The silicone is good, it’s just that all the qualities of the Echo SS don’t work well for me in tandem.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/posts/tantus-echo</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/posts/tantus-echo</guid>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
